(Sheldon:)say the word angry
over and over makes me feel?
Ooh, a-angry?
What are you doing?
I-I-I knew the answer.
I got excited.
(Leonard:)Hey, buddy, why don't
we go for a walk,
(Leonard:)so you can calm down.
(Sheldon:)That's a good idea.
(Sheldon:)I guess everyone's
having them now.
(Leonard:)Hey, I'm trying
to help you.
(Sheldon:)Fine.
(Sheldon:)You can walk ahead of me
and scare off the pigeons.
(Leonard:)Just wave your arms a little
and they fly away, it's not...
(Howard:)Okay, Raj,
(Howard:)I'm gonna
show you something.
(Sheldon:)Now,
(Howard:)one of us thinks it's offensive.
(Howard:)The other thinks it's hilarious
(Howard:)and a great idea.
(Howard:)But, I'm not
going to tell you
(Howard:)who likes it.
(Raj:)This is tough.
(Raj:)But I'm going to say